<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>

<root>
    <email>
        <emailType>
            mark as spam
        </emailType>
        <from>
            offers@gameripoffs.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            Extra 50% trade in credit
        </subject>
        <message>
            If you come in this weekend you will be able to take advantage of some great offers!
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            delete
        </emailType>
        <from>
            prince@totallyreal.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            Please Help Me!
        </subject>
        <message>
            I am a prince from a real place, I need your help. Please give your bank account information so I Can transfer money to your account!
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            reply
        </emailType>
        <from>
            teacher@highschool.edu
        </from>
        <subject>
            Latest test
        </subject>
        <message>
            I would like to talk to you about your latest test grades, please talk to me after class this week.
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            delete
        </emailType>
        <from>
            Gov@g0v.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            Security Breach
        </subject>
        <message>
            we recently has a security breach at the government, please us your social security number so we can verify you.
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            mark as spam
        </emailType>
        <from>
            offers@retailplaces.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            20% off
        </subject>
        <message>
            Come in this weekend for 20% off on select items.
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            mark as spam
        </emailType>
        <from>
            offers@wegotdeals.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            40% OFF ON SELECT ITEMS!!!!!!
        </subject>
        <message>
            SPECIAL DEALS, THIS WEEKEND ONLY. UP TO 40% OFF ON ALL ACCESSORIES AND 10% OFF ON ALL ELECTRONICS!
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            forward
        </emailType>
        <from>
            teacher@highschool.edu
        </from>
        <subject>
            programming team
        </subject>
        <message>
            I heard that you were interested in joining the programming team, please see my in my office this week for more information.
            Please forward this email to other students that may be interested as well.
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            delete
        </emailType>
        <from>
            hello@legitimate.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            check this out
        </subject>
        <message>
            check out this cool image I found on the internet, you just have to download the 5gb attachment to look at it!
        </message>
    </email>

    <email>
        <emailType>
            delete
        </emailType>
        <from>
            bankofbanks@bank5.com
        </from>
        <subject>
            free credit card
        </subject>
        <message>
            You have been approved a special credit card with a 45% interest rate and a limit of 5,000 dollars. please give us your bank info
            and social so we can confirm your new card.
        </message>
    </email>
</root>